blogmaverick.com 2005-05-20

# Weblogs, Inc. Home Page - www.weblogsinc.com _

## Weblogs, Inc. Privacy Statement

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Weblogs, Inc. websites (a.k.a. blogs) including [Engadget](http://www.engadget.com/), [Autoblog](http://www.autoblog.com/), [Blogging Baby](http://www.bloggingbaby.com/), [Joystiq](http://www.joystiq.com/) and all the websites run under the weblogsinc.com domain.

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.

## Email Addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don't currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

## Ownership of Information

Weblogs, Inc. is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

## Comments/Message Boards

Most Weblogs, Inc. websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce "comment spam." These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

## Cookies

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

## Third Party Cookies

Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. Weblogs, Inc. does not have access to this data.

## Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

## Legal proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Weblogs, Inc. may need to disclose information when required by law.

## Business Transitions

If Weblogs, Inc. is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

## Links

Weblogs, Inc. websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Weblogs, Inc.

## Notification of Changes

When Weblogs, Inc. makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Weblogs, Inc.**  
2200 Colorado Avenue, Suite 729  
Santa Monica, CA 90404  
Phone: 310-828-8284  
Fax: 310-861-0600

**Weblogs, Inc.**  
The Chrysler Building  
132 East 43rd Street, Suite 1000  
New York, New York 10017
